trailforks.com 2012-12-09

# Privacy Policy | Trailforks.com

This privacy policy sets out how "Trailforks" uses and protects any information that you give "Trailforks" when you use this website.

"Trailforks" is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

"Trailforks" may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

### Why do you collect personal information then?

The site collects information principally to verify you are a real person and not some sort of spambot before you participate in discussion, forums, post your content, etc.

### What does Trailforks do with registration information?

Nothing, honest! The details you enter when registering are completely private and will never be revealed to any third parties.

That said, some information is for public display or consumption, and this is made very clear when you enter it. Mostly this will be visible to other registered users only.

### Cookies

A cookie is a small file, which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

### Links to Other Websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide visiting such sites, and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
